let savollar10 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "absence",
      answer: "B. yo'qlik",
      options: [
        "A. mavjudlik",
        "B. yo'qlik",
        "C. kamchilik",
        "D. yuqotish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "aloud",
      answer: "C. ovoz chiqarib",
      options: [
        "A. sekin",
        "B. jim",
        "C. ovoz chiqarib",
        "D. aniq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "bald",
      answer: "A. kal",
      options: [
        "A. kal",
        "B. sochli",
        "C. jingalak",
        "D. oq sochli"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "blanket",
      answer: "D. adyol",
      options: [
        "A. yostiq",
        "B. choyshab",
        "C. gilam",
        "D. adyol"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to creep",
      answer: "B. asta yurmoq",
      options: [
        "A. yugurmoq",
        "B. asta yurmoq",
        "C. sakramoq",
        "D. emaklamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "divorce",
      answer: "C. ajralish",
      options: [
        "A. nikoh",
        "B. unashtuv",
        "C. ajralish",
        "D. ajrashish"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "to imitate",
      answer: "A. taqlid qilmoq",
      options: [
        "A. taqlid qilmoq",
        "B. nusxa olmoq",
        "C. o'ynamoq",
        "D. o'rganmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "infant",
      answer: "B. chaqaloq",
      options: [
        "A. bola",
        "B. chaqaloq",
        "C. go'dak",
        "D. o'smir"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to kidnap",
      answer: "D. odam o'g'irlamoq",
      options: [
        "A. tutmoq",
        "B. ushlamoq",
        "C. qamapoq",
        "D. odam o'g'irlamoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "nap",
      answer: "C. mizg'ish",
      options: [
        "A. uyqu",
        "B. dam",
        "C. mizg'ish",
        "D. tinchlik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "nowhere",
      answer: "B. hech qayerda",
      options: [
        "A. hamma joyda",
        "B. hech qayerda",
        "C. qayerdadir",
        "D. boshqa joyda"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to pat",
      answer: "A. sekin urmoq",
      options: [
        "A. sekin urmoq",
        "B. urmoq",
        "C. tegmoq",
        "D. silkimoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "relief",
      answer: "D. yengillik",
      options: [
        "A. quvonch",
        "B. baxt",
        "C. rohat",
        "D. yengillik"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "to reproduce",
      answer: "C. qayta yaratmoq",
      options: [
        "A. nusxa olmoq",
        "B. yasamoq",
        "C. qayta yaratmoq",
        "D. ishlab chiqarmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "rhyme",
      answer: "B. qofiya",
      options: [
        "A. she'r",
        "B. qofiya",
        "C. qo'shiq",
        "D. misra"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to suck",
      answer: "A. so'rmoq",
      options: [
        "A. so'rmoq",
        "B. ichmoq",
        "C. yalamoq",
        "D. shimmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "urgent",
      answer: "C. shoshilinch",
      options: [
        "A. muhim",
        "B. zarur",
        "C. shoshilinch",
        "D. kerakli"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to vanish",
      answer: "B. g'oyib bo'lmoq",
      options: [
        "A. ketmoq",
        "B. g'oyib bo'lmoq",
        "C. yo'qolmoq",
        "D. tark etmoq"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "wagon",
      answer: "A. arava",
      options: [
        "A. arava",
        "B. mashina",
        "C. qo'l arava",
        "D. yukxona"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "wrinkle",
      answer: "D. ajin",
      options: [
        "A. iz",
        "B. chiziq",
        "C. chandiq",
        "D. ajin"
      ]
    }
];

export default savollar10;